[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION.
THERE IS NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE OR EVENTS.
[♪ rock music playing]
EPISODE 1
[tires screech]
[♪ funky music plays]
Good morning! Hey, Daniel!
KARIN'S SWEET POTATO FARM
NO OVERTIME - TEMP WORKER FIRST-TIMERS WELCOME
-Good morning! -Whoa. [coughs]
Hey,
-good morning… -I brought you water.
Thank you.
But, uh, I wish you brought some help instead.
I wish I could have brought a hundred people to help.
But it's hard to find anyone who wants to do farm work with intensive labor.
[sighs]
[sighs] That's why the both of us will work extra hard. Okay?
[coughs] What?
That's too hard!
You really expect us to work this entire field ourselves?
Really? We can't.
It's impossible! [voice echoes]
Fine, then. We'll just get
-a thousand meters or so done. -What?
That's not much. All right. Time's a-ticking. Let's move it.
-Come on. -[groans]
-[in German] I'm dying out here. -[in English] Huh? What was that?
Uh, the sky's nice and clear.
[birds squawking]
What a nice day!
[♪ funky music continues]
Good morning.
Ah! Good morning, Grandma!
[Grandma laughs]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[in Korean] The pictures are turning out great here.
[friend 1] Yeah? Hey, let's take one together.
[friend 2] Sure, let's get someone to take it for us.
Would you like me to take it for you?
-[friend 2] Oh, would you? -Yeah.
Then could you take one of us together? Thank you.
Hey, isn't he the CEO of Y:SPACE?
Lee Yubin?
-[friend 1] Whoa, is that really him? -Yeah!
-[friend 1] No way. That's insane. -[friend 2] Wow, how cool! [chuckles]
Hey, that came out really pretty.
[friend 2] "Pretty"? Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, he said we look pretty! Hey, let's see.
Huh?
What is this?
MADE IT TO MONÉA, THE 2025 KME DESIGN AWARD WINNER, AT OPENING!
NO WAY, DID YOU SEE LEE YUBIN?
YES! HE'S WAY TOO HOT TO BE A SPATIAL DESIGNER
We displayed these individually. As for the candles…
[gasps]
Excuse me for a sec.
Boss. Hey, what are you doing here so early?
Huh? The opening's not for another two hours.
They're from the head office. This is our CEO, Lee Yubin.
Why don't you two introduce yourselves and…
Wow. Look at you, boss. Working so hard. [chuckles]
You're already… What? What is it?
[♪ comical music playing]
It's a little crooked…
Excuse me. Could you make sure these are lined up properly?
Yeah.
You haven't had your coffee yet, have you?
Yeah, let's go grab a nice, hot cup of coffee…
Hey, Yubin. Wait, boss. Yubin!
-How about some coffee? -Good evening, sir.
Come on, have some coffee!
-Hey. -Yeah?
What…
What is that?
Wait, you think…
You think that color goes with the rest of the space?
You really think a red table belongs here?
Just let it slide just this once, all right?
The client specifically asked for it. They're the one paying--
Whoa, boss! How are we supposed to defy the almighty client?
That thing's expensive! Please don't.
What's the condition in our client contracts?
"Lee Yubin's designs are never, ever to be altered."
[inhales sharply] Take it away.
I learn so much from you every day.
SPATIAL DESIGN GRAND PRIZE KOREAN ARCHITECTURE ASSOCIATION
SPATIAL DESIGN AWARD - WINNER
2023 GARDEN DESIGN AWARD
ASSOCIATION OF ARCHITECTS SPECIAL AWARD
[sighs]
[knocks on door]
♪ Want to have a drink with me? ♪
Come on, boss. You've got to learn to enjoy yourself once a project's over.
This was our first team dinner in six months.
You could've shown up.
Have you ever seen me at team dinners?
All a CEO needs to do is keep his mouth shut and pick up the bill.
Why make everyone uncomfortable?
You're so uptight.
[sighs] Ease up a little, will you?
That way, the staff might actually follow you…
Ease up?
Hey.
We put our company's reputation on the line to win this project.
All right? And we beat 100-to-1 odds to get it, no less.
Giving it all might still fall short.
-But you want me to ease up? -All right.
Yeah, you're right.
Once this project's finished, your name's going global.
I know that.
Here you go.
Cheers.
Now that the investors are finally done with their review,
looks like all that's left is for us to sign!
Hey, but this…
Are you sure this is legit?
-Huh? -I mean, this is a huge project,
and they're investing in a startup like us?
-Does that even make sense? -Lee Yubin.
You, our CEO. That's who they believe in.
The legal review's totally clear. Everything checks out.
-Good work. -[chuckles]
Oh, the contract. Here, you should look it over too.
It's fine. I'm sure you've handled it just fine.
Nah, come on.
I'm busy, man. You take care of it.
All right.
Don't worry about this kind of thing. You just focus on the design work, okay?
I'll take care of all the tedious stuff like this.
Oh, and this.
-Well, it was on my desk. -What is it?
I think the newbie got confused.
What's this? Japan?
Oh, sorry. I thought it was for me and opened it.
Hey, looks like your father left you some land in Japan.
INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR UNSETTLED INHERITANCE
[Yubin] You speak Japanese?
Well, Japan is a major market for us.
I had a quick look, and it's an island.
Imagine turning that island into a resort.
Huh?
Hey, take a closer look.
-Director Kim. -Yeah?
What, should we start another meeting now?
Wait… Start another meeting with you? No, I'd rather…
[gulps, groans]
Oh, boy.
Bongsu.
Bongsu!
[in English] Good night.
[in Korean] Geez.
NOTICE REGARDING THE SALE OF LAND
FARMLAND IN JAPAN REGISTERED UNDER THE LATE LEE GYEONGSU…
What is this? "Land sale"?
"Charo Island"?
KARIN'S STRAWBERRIES
[Karin, in English] Good morning. Long time no see.
-How are things? -Good morning.
Nice sweet potato harvest this year.
Yes, good morning! Mrs. Osono.
Freshly-harvested sweet potatoes.
Oh, Karin! Good morning!
Good morning. Here's a free sample just for you.
Your berries are ripe already?
And we're introducing a new variety next year.
When we do, please put them front and center.
You're certainly very skilled.
I hope that everything goes well for you this season.
You know I'll bring you the best ones. Be on the lookout, all right?
[shop owner] I've heard that one a few too many times.
Why bother with this variety? Doesn't even flower.
[Karin sighs]
With our strawberries, we ensure that Mother Nature ripens them naturally.
They're more delicious than any strawberry you've tasted.
Even if they take time more and effort, that's precisely why
ours are the best ones.
Oh, someone is cocky about her berries, huh?
You wanna bet on it?
Uh… I've got deliveries to run.
You're as strong-willed as ever, dear. [laughs]
Hey, once my strawberries have been officially certified,
then it's gonna be all over for everybody else.
[screams, in Korean] No! I'm not doing this!
-Hey, wait! -Let go of me.
What matters here is the model, okay?
Hey. Dang it!
Why's my hair looking like this?
And what's with that giant fan?
Huh?
-[fan whirring] -[director] Hey, hey!
Cut, cut.
Oh, shoot, this is…
My hair…
Shoot.
-Oh, boy. -[huffs]
Hey, don't look at things like that. "Y:SPACE is taking the world by storm."
[blows]
Look, we don't need any models or celebrities.
We need an ad with your face on it
to attract investors more easily.
How many times do I have to tell you, boss?
-Don't you… Ow. Don't you trust me? -I'm not doing it.
[huffs] Come on.
Hey, you're the CEO. The face of this company!
Our star! Okay?
Not happening.
Swedish furniture.
[Yubin whines] Swedish furniture…
If this goes well, you might finally get to collaborate
with that Swedish luxury furniture brand you were talking about, you know.
And if we go into next month's meeting with this ad,
we'll make a better impression.
I get it.
This is new to you.
You're uncomfortable.
But just bite the bullet and think, "This is for the future of our company,"
and give it a go.
They said once they touch it all up with CGI, it'll look amazing.
[crew member] All right, Yubin. Please stand by.
Oh, yeah, he's coming!
The gorgeous superstar Lee Yubin is on his way! He's coming!
[chuckles] Yep, he's on his way.
[♪ opera music playing]
[Yubin] Where every moment you stay comes alive.
Y:SPACE is taking the world by storm.
A space made just for you…
[grunts] Shoot.
Y:SPACE.
Smile, Yubin! Smile!
Dang it!
THE TWO FACES OF A STAR SPATIAL DESIGNER
Y:SPACE IS DONE FOR
THE POPULAR PLANNER, JUST A FIGUREHEAD ALL ALONG
WAS HE A CON ARTIST ALL ALONG?!
[♪ rock music playing]
[reporter] Lee Yubin, an internationally award-winning spatial designer,
has recently become embroiled in fraud allegations
related to an urban redevelopment project.
RECENTS KIM BONGSU
[automated voice] The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
Kim Bongsu!
How can we tell you anything when nothing's confirmed?
No, it's not like that. Please just leave your number.
-But we're not… -We cannot speak on this matter.
It's a surprise to us too. So how can we tell you anything?
Apparently, Director Kim took everything and ran.
Weren't the two of them supposed to be best friends?
[employee] Exactly.
What's Mr. Lee going to do?
He was betrayed by his friend, and now he's taking the fall. Geez.
Well, what's going to happen to our paychecks?
[door slams open]
-Where's Lee Yubin? -What's going on?
[clamoring]
[reporter] It was later revealed that Kim, a registered director and business partner
at Lee's company, Y:SPACE, collected the project's advance payments
in multiple installments before disappearing.
Although Lee maintains that he was not involved
in the business side of the project,
it won't be easy for him to escape legal and moral responsibility.
This is Kwon Gunam, IMP News.
[people clamoring]
Huh? What the… What's going on?
Where's my paycheck?
NOTICE OF BUSINESS CLOSURE
WE THANK EVERYONE WHO HAS SUPPORTED OUR COMPANY
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THIS ANNOUNCEMENT
AND ARE GRATEFUL FOR THE SUPPORT YOU HAVE SHOWN US
LEE YUBIN CEO OF Y:SPACE INC.
FOR RENT
[engine starts]
Geez.
[coughs]
-[friend] Geez. -[Yubin groans]
-What? Come on. -Kim Bongsu, that jerk.
I knew something was off. You can tell a lot from a person's face.
[Yubin] Couldn't you have come in a little later? It's too early.
-Geez. -Hey, it's broad daylight. Get up.
How can you be so relaxed?
You sold your place with no backup plan.
TAX ACCOUNTANT CHOI HYEJIN
-What are you going to do now? -I don't know, okay? I don't!
I don't know. Everyone was up in arms, demanding their money back.
-What choice did I have? -Hold on.
What's with those pajamas? Don't tell me they're designer.
Why didn't you sell those?
How could I sell these? They're my dignity.
Would you sell your dignity?
Maybe it'll take sleeping on the street to knock some sense into you.
[Yubin groans] Dang it.
[sighs] Whatever.
Anyway, the urgent stuff's mostly taken care of.
I scraped together enough to pay all the employees' severance too.
I'm completely broke now.
Well, not completely.
What?
Looks like you still have some inherited assets.
Huh? Assets?
A piece of land in Japan under your father's name.
NOTICE REGARDING SALE OF LAND
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Right! Oh, yeah.
Oh, the land. I've got land.
Since it's overseas property, it's a bit complicated.
Okay.
But it's a pretty sizeable piece of land, so if you sell it at a good price…
Hey, okay. Hang on.
So what do I do from here?
AKATSUKI CITY GREEN NOVA CORPORATION
[in English] Now I'll need the documents on your crop variety…
I marked it with a red sticky note. Ah! I found it. Here it is.
Thank you. It's my first year here. I'm sorry it's taking a while.
Don't worry. You can take your time.
-This is it? -Uh-huh.
That's all the relevant documents we need from you.
As for the next step…
Crop inspection.
Yes, that's right. You're an expert at this.
Well, this is my third year coming here,
and my third year attempt at passing this.
Uh, you seem thoroughly prepared.
That's why I'm sure that you'll succeed.
Thank you very much.
I've heard that three years in a row now, but I appreciate it.
I'm terribly sorry.
[chuckles] It's no big deal.
For some reason, I have a really good feeling this year.
-[laughs] -Oh, that's good.
So it's a decent size, and the pH of the soil is stable.
I told you. The strawberries are very good.
They're tart, high in natural sugar, and have the best aroma…
Oh, I'd say you're not quite out of the woods yet.
I didn't see you standing there.
You nearly scared me half to death, sir.
Paperwork is easy. It's the crop inspection that really gets you.
-You know that? -I'm well aware and prepared.
I've seen my grandfather go through this process again and again.
Quiz. Tagawa, off the top of your head,
tell me what it takes to pass crop inspection. Let's hear it, kid.
Over 80% of the field, uh, must bear fruit.
Also, the consistency of the fruit's size,
its firmness and sweetness,
must match what's listed in the submitted paperwork.
Oh. There you have it.
-[sigh] -[Karin chuckles]
Well, feel free to stop by anytime.
I'll show you the best strawberries you'll ever taste.
[laughs]
I'd be happy to come by.
You're going to surpass your grandfather as a farmer if you keep going like that.
So I'll see you in three days for the crop inspection.
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
Oh! I'm gonna miss the ferry! See you later.
-Thank you as always! -Have a nice ride back.
Bye!
[ferry horn blows]
FUKUOKA PIER - FERRY TERMINAL 1
[Yubin] Thank you.
[in Korean] Hey, they only run three ferries a day to the island.
How tiny is this place?
[Hyejin] You got all the paperwork ready, right?
Yeah. I'll just take one last look around and head straight back.
Why? Since you're there, why not stay and relax for a bit?
Hey, are you kidding me? What's there to do on that tiny little island?
[announcer, in English] Dear passengers, the ferry bound for Charo Island…
-[in Korean] I think it's here. Gotta go. -[in English] …will disembark momentarily.
If you have not boarded the ferry yet please gather…
-Charo Island, please. -Charo Island.
Oh. [chuckles]
This is the last ticket.
-What? -Huh?
[Yubin, in Korean] Is he saying there's only one ticket left?
[in English] Uh, do you mind if I buy the last ticket?
[in Korean] Sorry? No, I mean… What's she saying?
[in English] I-- I'm Korean.
-I'm sorry. -Oh. You're Korean… [stammers]
[clears throat] I'm in a hurry. Could you let me buy the ticket?
[in Korean] I'm really sorry, but I've got something important too. I'm sorry.
[groaning]
[in English] I'm not feeling so great. Could I…
[in Korean] What? You were sprinting just fine a second ago.
[Karin clears throat]
[in English] Well, I was here first, before you.
[in Korean] But I touched the counter first.
[sighs]
[automated voice, in English] Rock, scissors, paper.
-Huh? -Rock, scissors, paper…
[in Korean] Rock… Rock, paper, scissors?
-Hurry up. -No, come on.
We're not actually doing rock, paper, scissors for a ticket, are we?
[in English] Give up?
"Give up"?
-[in Korean] Rock, paper, scissors! -[in English] Hey, I wasn't ready.
[Yubin thinking, in Korean] Welcome to the ruthless world of competition.
[in English] Ready, go.
Ready, go.
[in Korean] Ugh! I should've thrown rock! I should've…
Hey, listen. In Korea, we do best two out of three. One more round, please.
[in English] Welcome to the cutthroat world of competition, sir.
EXIT
Oh, it's Daniel!
Daniel! Daniel!
Daniel! Hang on.
You can't leave yet!
I'm sorry. I can't stay any longer.
No, Daniel, you can't go. I need you to stay here.
-I can't do it by myself. -Not my problem.
-Daniel, please… -Let go!
You have to stay! I need you!
You're the strongest man I've ever met in my entire life!
What?
[in Korean] What is she doing?
[in English] You beg me every day to go harder and put my muscle into it.
I don't have the stamina to do what you want.
-Please, don't leave me. -[in Korean] Wow, she's intense.
[Karin, in English] Is it money? I'll give you so much money…
How much do you want?
I don't want anything.
-Give it to me. -Please. Think this over.
Don't be rash. Stay. I need you. Stay!
[grunts] Stay!
You cheated!
-Daniel, please! -Let me go!
[Karin] Don't leave!
"Could I have a copy of the plat map?"
Could I have a copy of…
COULD I HAVE A COPY OF THE PLAT MAP?
"Could I have a copy of the plat map?"
"Could I…"
Oh, uh…
[♪ pop music playing on radio]
[in Korean] I don't even like these anymore.
Just one a day, okay?
Don't eat like a dozen and get an earful from your mom again like last time.
Have you been guarding her well while I was away?
Guarding her?
What am I, a dog?
Hey, are you already going through puberty?
You'll be working here in Korea for a while, right?
I've got to go back in a week.
And this time, I'll be away a bit longer.
Why don't you just move there?
They still make these, huh?
[in English] Where did my candy go?
Under here?
It's not there.
[in Korean] Looking for this?
[in English] Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. [chuckles]
[sighs]
[in Korean] I'll just sell it off and be done with it.
Should be simple enough.
[in English] It's not that easy.
Please, sir. Can you really not find anyone?
I asked around, but no one's available.
No one who wants to work on your farm, anyway.
Huh? Why not?
The work is physically demanding, there's nothing to do on the island,
and they're all terrified of the owner.
What? They think that I'm--
Oh, whatever. I'm nice. I'm not terrifying at all.
Listen, Karin, what if you call it quits? Do something easier?
Somebody your size isn't made for farm work.
[sighs] You listen.
I've worked five years on my own
and ten with my grandfather before that.
On top of that, if your strawberries don't get certified this time,
your relief aid will get pulled.
Aren't you worried?
Yes, of course I am, and that's why this whole thing matters!
You know that as well as I do.
Karin, calm down.
Even so…
finding any new employees around here,
it's certainly not easy.
Ah…
Hmm?
Karin, what have you got there?
Where'd you get that?
It's a really expensive bottle.
I know. It's your favorite, right?
[both chuckle]
Whoa!
Mmm, mmm! [chuckles]
Oh! Oh.
So, you sure you can't find anyone?
Well… what sort of employee are you looking for?
I'll make sure to find you the right fit.
[child] He's throwing up!
[people exclaiming]
Firstly, they need to be strong…
[retching]
[children exclaiming]
[in Korean] What…
Come on, how come I can't get a signal?
Come on, give me a signal already.
Geez! Why won't it connect?
-[in English] …a pleasant personality… -Right.
But as for looks…
Anything works. Doesn't matter.
Oh! Hello!
CHARO ISLAND VILLAGE BUS HAMANOKUCHI - IRIE
NEXT IS SHIOHAMA
-The next bus isn't coming for a while. -Hey?
They only run three a day. You just missed one.
Look. See? No buses. Where you heading?
I can give you a ride. Just hop in.
Come on.
I don't have all day here.
[groans]
-Hurry up, would you? -[in Korean] Wait, no more buses.
[in English] I said I'd take you. Get in the car.
[groans] I'm okay, thank you.
-Get in here. Come on. -I… Okay.
-Hop in. -I'm okay.
-And now it's pouring. [sighs] -[Yubin exclaims]
[screams]
[in Korean] I'll take that ride! I'll take it!
-[in English] Help. Help me, help me. -Buckle up.
Help me, help me.
[in Korean] Shoot… This weather… It's going to be okay, right?
[in English] What are you gonna do over at the village office?
[in Korean] Sorry?
Uh, uh, uh…
Hold on.
[in English] It's fine. Forget about it.
How about some music?
[♪ haunting music playing]
[driver humming along]
[in Korean] This feels a little off.
MAP SEARCH
[♪ haunting music continues]
Karin?
-[in English] Hey, why are you still here? -Mari!
Ah, you're here. I'm so glad.
You forgot to bring your medication again, didn't you?
That's why I tried to get home as soon as possible, but Daniel…
What about my sweet little Daniel?
Huh?
Yesterday, Daniel and I, um, kind of…
He took off.
-What? -Daniel quit today.
-He went back to Germany. -[gasps]
[whimpers] Just when I finally let him kiss me.
No way. Ugh.
Is that what he was planning to do all along?
Is that why he kissed me so passionately?
Oh, how annoying.
[whimpers]
-Hey! Wait till you're back on the island. -Why?
The tarot cards said that we had a strong bond.
-Stop! I need a drink! Come on! -Knock it off.
-Let go! -Wait until we're back!
[Yubin] Whoa.
[exclaiming]
[♪ tense music playing]
[in English] I gotta take care of something.
[Yubin, in Korean] What? What is it?
[gasps]
[♪ tense music builds]
[exclaims]
No!
[thunder crashes]
-[in English] This is a bad omen. -Huh? What is?
I mean, look at the cards. The queen represents you.
At first, you seem frail.
-But you're resilient deep down. -Mm-hmm.
Seven of Cups represents a situation with way too many choices.
It could be a fantasy, or it could become reality.
Is that a bad thing?
The outcome would be up to you, my friend.
-Tarot cards are such a sham. -You need to believe in it, Karin.
Why? They were wrong about Daniel, right?
They didn't predict him leaving.
It's easiest to miss what's right under your nose.
[chuckles] Tell me what this shiny one means.
[gasps] It's the Wheel…
of Fortune.
It means you're bound to have a fated encounter
camouflaged as a coincidence in the near future.
It means fate?
[in Korean] Where am I?
[groans] I'm screwed. My phone's dying too.
[exclaims]
[sighs] I'm screwed.
I'm screwed.
[whimpers]
I left all my stuff back there.
[shouts]
Dang it!
[in English] Excuse me!
[in Korean] Hey!
[exclaims]
Come on, seriously.
[groans] This place is just not for me.
[♪ operatic music playing]
[gasps]
[in English] Why did you run away?
Huh?
CHARO VILLAGE OFFICE
[Yubin] Thank you so much.
-Thank you so much. -Huh. Strange.
Karin already lives on the plot of land that you own.
It's better to go and have yourselves a little chat.
-Uh-- -Uh, you don't understand.
Hey, Kunam, you know where Karin lives.
-Can you give this guy a ride? -[gasps]
[♪ whistling tunelessly]
Oh…
Here we are.
Thank you very much.
-Are you all right? -Huh?
[chuckles]
[Yubin, in Korean] I think I'm right about this.
[shouting, in Korean] Oh, my God…
[in broken Korean] "Oh, my God." [in English] Is that right?
[chuckles] "Oh, my God, Oh, my God" in Korean?
[in Korean] Right? Yeah?
Come on, I knew it. You're Korean.
[in English] I don't…
-[in Korean] You're right. I am. -Geez.
Can I get your number? I think I'm going to need your help.
I don't really speak the language here, so… Yeah?
[in English] What a pain.
[in Korean] All right, thanks.
-[phone buzzing] -Calling. [in English] Okay.
Okay. Block.
-[in Korean] I know what "blocked" means. -Feel free to call me, sir.
[engine starts]
[sighs]
So is this it?
What's that?
STRAWBERRY PICKING KAMINOSAWA FARM
ALL YOU CAN EAT
-[in English] Hey… -Huh?
I was thinking…
What if the tarot cards were describing my strawberries?
Strawberries? That would be sad, don't you think?
Sad? Why? I spent three years tending to my precious strawberries,
and now they're finally getting recognition.
-[sighs] -I couldn't be prouder of them.
You think your strawberries have personalities?
-Yeah, in some ways, they-- -Mari, you're here.
Ooh. What great timing.
-I'll hold it. -Thank you.
Didn't I tell you? Kunam is totally head over heels for you.
[chuckles] Yeah, well, he's not my type at all.
Do you want to get dinner together?
-Karin, do you wanna come too? -I can join?
-Mm-hmm. -I almost forgot!
There's some guy waiting for you at your place.
Who is it? Do you know? What guy?
Maybe Daniel's replacement?
-Not that quickly. No way. -What did he look like? Was he hot?
Was he hot? Not hotter than me. Come on.
Sorry, Mari. I've gotta check.
-See you later. -What? Hey, wait!
It's just us.
Sure. Why not?
Come on.
Yay!
[Yubin] "Karin Farm"?
[in Korean] What is this?
Wait, is someone living here or what?
Is this a farm?
Wait, what the hell's going on here?
Is someone living here?
[children laughing, clamoring]
[teacher, in English] Slow down! Careful!
Don't lose your buddy!
Excuse me. Can you tell me where the strawberry picking is?
Over there? Or here?
Uh… [speaks Japanese]
-[in Korean] What? -[in English] Right there!
Yay! Strawberries!
[teacher] Be careful down the stairs!
[child] Look at this one!
-[in Korean] Well, this is… -[child, in English] Over here!
[in Korean] Is this one of those strawberry-picking places?
-[in English] Karin. -Oh, you're back!
-I'm back. -So how was it? Will you pass this year?
Mm-hmm. Green Nova is coming to inspect in three days,
but I feel good about it.
If 80% of my crop bears fruit, then I'll pass.
[children screaming, clamoring]
I've got this!
-That's good. -That's great to hear.
[Karin] Right?
Ah!
-Here. -[in Korean] Oh, these?
[in English] Thank you very much.
[in Korean] Okay.
Mmm.
[children shouting]
-[in English] Hi there. -[child] Hello.
-[chuckles] Hi. -Hello.
Hello.
[child] Yay!
[gasps]
What happened? What…
What? This can't be…
What?
Over 80% of the field, uh, must bear fruit.
[agency owner] On top of that,
if your strawberries don't get certified this time,
then your relief aid will get pulled.
Are you sure you're not worried?
[beeping]
[in Korean] Are you the owner of…
Huh?
[in English] What are you doing?
[watch beeping]
[beeping accelerates]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
MERRY BERRY LOVE
NEXT EPISODE
You walked onto my private property and you single-handedly ruined everything.
You're the new field worker?
[Karin] He doesn't look like he's touched dirt in his entire life.
[Yubin, in Korean] People fight. That's how you get close and build a bond.
[♪ upbeat music plays]